{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549043023123","data":{"timestamp":" 1549043023123"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_204205"," gameId":" 70c15e2a-54e4-47e4-a963-356e749c995e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ndani_kubwa-ndani-kuwa-wote"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ndani"," userResponse":" kubwa"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549043025797","data":{"timestamp":" 1549043025797"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_204205"," gameId":" 70c15e2a-54e4-47e4-a963-356e749c995e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ndani_kubwa-ndani-kuwa-wote"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ndani"," userResponse":" ndani"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549043099727","data":{"timestamp":" 1549043099726"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_204205"," gameId":" 70c15e2a-54e4-47e4-a963-356e749c995e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ndani_kubwa-ndani-kuwa-wote"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549043099792","data":{"timestamp":" 1549043099792"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_204205"," gameId":" 70c15e2a-54e4-47e4-a963-356e749c995e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akajikokota tena akarudi hadi ____________."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:all.asc.A..Z.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549043138642","data":{"timestamp":" 1549043138642"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_204205"," gameId":" c657531e-9d91-444d-82cd-4e989ff3fb90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_all.asc.A..Z.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:all.asc.A..Z.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549043149969","data":{"timestamp":" 1549043149969"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_204205"," gameId":" c657531e-9d91-444d-82cd-4e989ff3fb90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_all.asc.A..Z.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" Q"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:all.asc.A..Z.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549043172475","data":{"timestamp":" 1549043172475"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_204205"," gameId":" c657531e-9d91-444d-82cd-4e989ff3fb90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_all.asc.A..Z.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:all.asc.A..Z.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549043188533","data":{"timestamp":" 1549043188533"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_204205"," gameId":" c657531e-9d91-444d-82cd-4e989ff3fb90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_all.asc.A..Z.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:all.asc.A..Z.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549043202942","data":{"timestamp":" 1549043202942"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_204205"," gameId":" c657531e-9d91-444d-82cd-4e989ff3fb90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_all.asc.A..Z.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_b"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:all.asc.A..Z.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549043222261","data":{"timestamp":" 1549043222260"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_204205"," gameId":" c657531e-9d91-444d-82cd-4e989ff3fb90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_all.asc.A..Z.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" c"," userResponse":" c"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:all.asc.A..Z.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549043236084","data":{"timestamp":" 1549043236084"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_204205"," gameId":" c657531e-9d91-444d-82cd-4e989ff3fb90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_all.asc.A..Z.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:all.asc.A..Z.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549043249595","data":{"timestamp":" 1549043249595"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_204205"," gameId":" c657531e-9d91-444d-82cd-4e989ff3fb90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_all.asc.A..Z.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_d"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:all.asc.A..Z.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549043265441","data":{"timestamp":" 1549043265441"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_204205"," gameId":" c657531e-9d91-444d-82cd-4e989ff3fb90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_all.asc.A..Z.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_d"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:all.asc.A..Z.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549043279759","data":{"timestamp":" 1549043279759"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_204205"," gameId":" c657531e-9d91-444d-82cd-4e989ff3fb90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_all.asc.A..Z.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_d"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:all.asc.A..Z.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549043294723","data":{"timestamp":" 1549043294722"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_204205"," gameId":" c657531e-9d91-444d-82cd-4e989ff3fb90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_all.asc.A..Z.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_d"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:all.asc.A..Z.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549043315723","data":{"timestamp":" 1549043315723"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_204205"," gameId":" c657531e-9d91-444d-82cd-4e989ff3fb90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_all.asc.A..Z.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_d"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:all.asc.A..Z.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549043326362","data":{"timestamp":" 1549043326361"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_204205"," gameId":" c657531e-9d91-444d-82cd-4e989ff3fb90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_all.asc.A..Z.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_e"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:all.asc.A..Z.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549043332919","data":{"timestamp":" 1549043332919"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_204205"," gameId":" c657531e-9d91-444d-82cd-4e989ff3fb90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_all.asc.A..Z.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_e"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:all.asc.A..Z.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549043339333","data":{"timestamp":" 1549043339333"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_204205"," gameId":" c657531e-9d91-444d-82cd-4e989ff3fb90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_all.asc.A..Z.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_e"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:all.asc.A..Z.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549043341340","data":{"timestamp":" 1549043341340"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_204205"," gameId":" c657531e-9d91-444d-82cd-4e989ff3fb90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_all.asc.A..Z.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_e"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:all.asc.A..Z.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549043346397","data":{"timestamp":" 1549043346397"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_204205"," gameId":" c657531e-9d91-444d-82cd-4e989ff3fb90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_all.asc.A..Z.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_e"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:all.asc.A..Z.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549043381243","data":{"timestamp":" 1549043381243"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_204205"," gameId":" c657531e-9d91-444d-82cd-4e989ff3fb90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_all.asc.A..Z.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_e"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:all.asc.A..Z.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549043394241","data":{"timestamp":" 1549043394241"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_204205"," gameId":" c657531e-9d91-444d-82cd-4e989ff3fb90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_all.asc.A..Z.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_e"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549043399523","data":{"timestamp":" 1549043399523"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_204205"," gameId":" 0929af2b-7593-4b8b-86e5-5a63a2143092"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" START"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549043415222","data":{"timestamp":" 1549043415222"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_204205"," gameId":" 0929af2b-7593-4b8b-86e5-5a63a2143092"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" END"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549043415249","data":{"timestamp":" 1549043415248"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_204205"," gameId":" 0929af2b-7593-4b8b-86e5-5a63a2143092"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549043415364","data":{"timestamp":" 1549043415364"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_204205"," gameId":" 0929af2b-7593-4b8b-86e5-5a63a2143092"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ENDPROBLEM"," userResponse":" ENDPROBLEM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" ENDPROBLEM"}},
{"end":"end"}]}